plaveb.com 2009-09-01

# Plaveb.com | company privacy policy statement

Plaveb is committed to protecting privacy and personal information that visitors may provide for information purposes. This information is necessary in order to provide you proper service. User information is only being used for particular project purposes and will not be distributed, sold or rented for any reason to third party. In the unlikely event that we choose to do so in the future with trustworthy external resources, you will be notified by email and given the opportunity to notify us not to share your personal information with any other external party.

Our site’s different registration/contact forms requires user to provide contact and company information. We use this information to contact you back and to serve you better.

You recognize and understand that there is no obligation on you to provide Plaveb with your personal information. Also information provided by you is with your full consent and own decision. You understand that we are under no obligation to verify the accuracy of information source whomever it concerns and we assume that is provided by you with your full consensus unless notified by you regarding fallacy of particular information. You also agree to provide correct information to avoid fraudulent activity.

#### Security and Data Protection

Plaveb takes every precaution to protect your personal information. When you submit or view sensitive information via our website, your information is protected, both online and offline. All financial transactions and otherwise sensitive information is protected using 128 bit Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

#### External Links

Plaveb website may have links to other websites and affiliates. Plaveb is not responsible for the content or the privacy of these affiliated websites or any other links that redirect user to external sites.

#### Connectivity Data

Plaveb may log IP addresses and or end systems information for better web administration. This information is used for analysis, diagnostics and to maintain the integrity of our services.

For any questions about privacy and similar issues, please contact us at [privacy@plaveb.com.](mailto:privacy@plaveb.com)
